Guide to the K. Leroy Irvis Papers, 1946-1995 AIS.1971.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Subject Files, 1945-1978; V.
  - Political Subject Files (1979 Addition), 1945-1978; 4.
    This subseries consists of reports, statements, brochures, correspondence, news clippings, remarks, newsletters, speeches, and notes all related to politics. They include files on education, legislature, prison reform, and speaking engagements. The files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Budgets and Taxes - Newspaper Clippings, 1968-1976 (Box 42, Folder 8-9)
    - Business (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Conferences (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Consumer Protection (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Education: University of Pittsburgh - Dollars that Make the Difference Campaign, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Education: University of Pittsburgh - FAS Gazette, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Education: University of Pittsburgh - Newspapers (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Education: University of Pittsburgh - Trustees (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Education: University of Pittsburgh - Western Psychiatric Institute (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Education: University of Pittsburgh - Miscellaneous, 1971-1975 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Education: SUNY Albany Alumni (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Education: SUNY Albany Alumni Newspapers (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Education: Pennsylvania Colleges (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Education: Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Election, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Environment (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Government Reform (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Health and Welfare (Box 44, Folder 26-27)
    - Labor, Jobs (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Legislature, 1959-1971 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Legislature, 1971-1977 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Legislature - Newspaper Clippings (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Legislature - House Bills (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Minority Concerns (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Organizations (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Prison Reform, 1970-1976 (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Prison Reform - Neighborhood Centers Youth Service Bureau Grant Application (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Prison Reform - Report on Allegations of Police Misconduct and Abuse After the Fatal Shooting of Pittsburgh Police Officer Patrick J. Wallace, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Prison Reform - Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1976 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Speaking Engagements Programs, 1945-1974 (Box 46, Folder 39-41)
    - Speaking Engagements Programs, 1975-1978 (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Transit (Box 47, Folder 43)
- Correspondence, 1945-2007; VI.
  This series consists primarily of Irvis's professional correspondence with constituents, legislators and other government officials, staffers, and community organizers during his legislative career. Also included are related items, such as job applications sent to Irvis's office and formal invitations. Finally, there is a substantial amount of correspondence about the University of Pittsburgh contained in Subseries iv of this series.
  This series has been arranged into four subseries by the date the material was acquired by the University of Pittsburgh. Subseries 3 and 4 of this series also contain a substantial amount of personal correspondence; other personal correspondence, some with fellow legislators, can be found in Series II: Personal. Additional community-related and election-related correspondence can be found in Series VII: Community and Series VIII: Campaigns, respectively.
  - Correspondence (1971 Original Deposit), 1965-1969; 1.
    This subseries consists primarily of correspondence from constituents but also includes correspondence about professional licensure and correspondence regarding miscellaneous conferences. The records are arranged by subject.
    - Elnora L. Head, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 356)
    - Miscellaneous requests involving Rep. William S. Morehead's office, 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 357)
    - Employment, 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 358-359)
    - Employment, House of Representatives, 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 360)
    - Academic admissions, requests for scholarships, etc., 1965-1969 (Box 22, Folder 361)
    - Mental and correctional institutions admissions, transfers, etc., 1967-1969 (Box 22, Folder 362)
    - Professional licensure, 1967, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 363)
    - Miscellaneous conferences, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 364)
  - Correspondence (1974 Addition), 2.
    This subseries contains Irvis's professoinal correspondence, including job applications, correspondence about scholarships, invitations, crank letters, as well as a folder of memos. General correspondence is arranged alphabetically, but some is arranged by subject.
    - Correspondence, A-B, 1971-1972 (Box 23, Folder 16-18)
    - Correspondence, C-U, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 2-15)
    - Correspondence, C-H, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 19-25)
    - Correspondence, H-P, 1971-1972 (Box 25, Folder 26-33)
    - Correspondence, R-Z, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 34-41)
    - Correspondence, January-February 1972 (Box 26, Folder 42-44)
    - Correspondence, March-June 1972 (Box 27, Folder 45-51)
    - Correspondence, July-October 1972 (Box 28, Folder 52-59)
    - Correspondence, November 1972 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence, Job Applications, (REMOVED) (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence, Scholarships, Financial Assistance (REMOVED) (Box 29, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence, Thank You Letters (Box 29, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence, Invitations (Box 29, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence, Richard Partee's Letters (Box 29, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence, Crank Letters (Box 29, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence, Confidential, (REMOVED) (Box 29, Folder 67)
    - Memos, Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence (1979 Addition), 1948-1978; 3.
    This subseries contains correspondence to and from state officials, as well as communication from constituents and personal letters. Materials are arranged chronologically.
    - Correspondence, 1948-1959 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, August-October, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, November-December, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence- Notes and Messages, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence (2010 Addition), 1945-2007; 4.
    The correspondence in this subseries is mainly incoming communication to Irvis from state officials, constituents, staff, or personal family and friends. The subseries also contains a large collection of personal greeting cards to the Irvis', some of which have been received from state officials. The correspondence subseries has been arranged according to its personal, community involvement, legislative, or University of Pittsburgh oriented nature. The subject matter of some correspondence overlaps between two of the aforementioned topics, so a majority of the correspondence has been identified as personal in nature. This subseries is arranged chronologically by date.
    - Personal, 1945 (Box 95, Folder 29)
    - Personal, 1946 (Box 95, Folder 30)
    - Personal, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 31)
    - Personal, 1951 (Box 95, Folder 32)
    - Personal, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 33)
    - Personal, 1953 (Box 95, Folder 34)
    - Personal, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 35)
    - Personal, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 36)
    - Personal, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 37)
    - Personal, 1957 (Box 95, Folder 38)
    - Personal, 1958 (Box 95, Folder 39)
    - Personal, 1959 (Box 95, Folder 40)
    - Personal, 1960 (Box 95, Folder 41)
    - Personal, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 42)
    - Personal, 1963 (Box 95, Folder 43)
    - Personal, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 44)
    - Personal, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 45)
    - Personal, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 46)
    - Personal, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 47)
    - Personal, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 48)
    - Personal, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 49)
    - Personal, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 50)
    - Personal, 1971 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Personal, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Personal, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Personal, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Personal, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Personal, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Personal, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Personal, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Personal, 1979 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Personal, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Personal, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Personal, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Personal, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Personal, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Personal, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Personal, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Personal, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Personal, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Personal, 1989 (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Personal, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Personal, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Personal, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Personal, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Personal, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Personal, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Personal, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - Personal, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Personal, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - Personal, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Personal, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Personal, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Personal, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Personal, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Personal, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Personal, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Personal, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Personal, 1996 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Personal, 1997 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Personal, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Personal, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Personal, 1998 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Personal, 1999 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Personal, 1999 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Personal, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Personal, 2001 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Personal, 2002 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Personal, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Personal, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Personal, 2003 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Personal, 2004 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Personal, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Personal, 2006 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Personal, 2006 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Personal, 2006 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Personal, 2006 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Personal, 2007 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Personal, undated (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Personal, undated (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Personal, undated (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Personal, undated (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Personal, undated (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Personal, undated (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Personal, undated (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Personal, undated (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Community Involvement, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Community Involvement, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Community Involvement, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Community Involvement, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Community Involvement, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Community Involvement, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Legislative, 1958 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - Legislative, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - Legislative, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Legislative, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Legislative, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Legislative, 1964 (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Legislative, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - Legislative, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - Legislative, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - Legislative, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - Legislative, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 30)
    - Legislative, 1975 (Box 99, Folder 31)
    - Legislative, 1976 (Box 99, Folder 32)
    - Legislative, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 33)
    - Legislative, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 34)
    - Legislative, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 35)
    - Legislative, 1980 (Box 99, Folder 36)
    - Legislative, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 37)
    - Legislative, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 38)
    - Legislative, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 39)
    - Legislative, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 40)
    - Legislative, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 41)
    - Legislative, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 42)
    - Legislative, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 43)
    - Legislative, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Legislative, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Legislative, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Legislative, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Legislative, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Legislative, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Legislative, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Legislative, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Legislative, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Legislative, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Legislative, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Legislative, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Legislative, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Legislative, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Legislative, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Legislative, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Legislative, 2004 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Legislative, 2005 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Legislative, 2006 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Legislative, undated (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1976 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 28)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 29)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1985 (Box 100, Folder 30)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 31)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1988 (Box 100, Folder 32)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1989 (Box 100, Folder 33)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 35)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 36)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1993 (Box 100, Folder 37)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 38)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 39)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1996 (Box 100, Folder 40)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 41)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 42)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 1999 (Box 100, Folder 43)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 44)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 45)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2002 (Box 100, Folder 46)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2003 (Box 100, Folder 47)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2005 (Box 100, Folder 48)
    - University of Pittsburgh, 2006 (Box 100, Folder 49)
    - University of Pittsburgh, undated (Box 100, Folder 50)
- Community, 1945-2005; VII.
  Irvis was active in community organizations and programs, particularly ones related to arts and culture, racial justice and equality, housing, and education. This series documents his involvement with many of those organizations through correspondence, publications, programs and pamphlets created by the organizations, reports, press releases, and newsclippings. It also documents some of Irvis's early employment in community-related enterprises, such as his time at the Urban League, with the Pittsburgh Courier, and as a law clerk and practicing lawyer.
  This series has been divided into subseries based on both the date the material was acquired by the University of Pittsburgh as well as by subject.
  - Community Programs (1980 addition), 1970-1978; 1.
    This subseries contains memos, correspondence, brochures, reports, and press releases related to community events in the Pittsburgh area, 1970-1978. This series is arranged chronologically.
    - 1970 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Irvis's Early Employment (1980 addition), 1945-1955; 2.
    This subseries contains clippings, programs, correspondence, and other materials related to Irvis' employment, 1945-1955. These file are arranged by subject.
    - Urban League, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Law School (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Courier, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Law Clerk Appointment, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - District Attorney and Rose, Schmidt, Dixon (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Museums, Programs, and Committees (1995 addition), 1971-1994; 3.
    This subseries contains clippings, programs brochures, correspondence, press releases, reports, and statements relating to various, cultural, civic, and educational organizations that Irvis has been associated. This series is arranged alphabetically by organization.
    - Afro-American Historical and Cultural Museum (AAHCM), 1992, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 93)
    - AAHCM (Box 65, Folder 94-96)
    - Action-Housing, INC (Box 65, Folder 97)
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development (Box 65, Folder 98)
    - Allegheny County Bicentennial (Box 65, Folder 99)
    - Allegheny Home Rule Charter, July 11, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 100)
    - Annual Legislative School Art Exhibition (Box 65, Folder 101)
    - Associated Artists of Pittsburgh (Box 65, Folder 102)
    - Bicentennial Subcommittee, September 18, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 103)
    - Bidwell Training Center (Box 65, Folder 104)
    - Biographical Dictionary of Early Pennsylvania Legislators (Box 65, Folder 105)
    - The Carnegie Museum - Art/Artifact: African Art (Box 66, Folder 106)
    - Catholic Charities of the Diocese of Pittsburgh (Box 66, Folder 107)
    - Child Lures(Child Abuse Prevention) (Box 66, Folder 108)
    - Franklin Institute Science Museum, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 109)
    - Higher Education, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 110)
    - Institute for Court Management of the National Center for State Court, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 111)
    - K. Leroy Irvis Towers, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 112)
    - Lemington Home for the Aged (Box 66, Folder 113)
    - Mobilizing for Adult Literacy and Learning, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 114)
    - Murray - Irvis Genetic Disease Center (Box 66, Folder 115)
    - Novak Report, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 116)
    - Nursing Recruitment Coalition (NRC) (Box 66, Folder 117)
    - Olympic Committee, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 118)
    - Pennsylvania Citizens for Better Libraries (PCBL) (Box 66, Folder 119)
    - Philadelphia Chamber of Commerce (Box 66, Folder 120)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art (Box 67, Folder 121-122)
    - Pittsburgh Convention Center, 1978 (Box 67, Folder 123)
    - Greater Pittsburgh Magazine, 1971 (Box 67, Folder 124)
    - Project 90 - Speaker (Box 67, Folder 125)
    - Public Support for the Gifted and Talented Education, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 126)
    - Shooting Star Productions, INC (Box 67, Folder 127)
    - Sixteen Black Artists (Box 67, Folder 128)
    - South Africa (Box 67, Folder 129)
    - Speeches and Eulogies (Box 67, Folder 130)
    - The Student Conservation Program, 1983 (Box 67, Folder 131)
  - Community Involvement (2010 addition), 1947-2005; 4.
    Irvis used his legislative influence from the Pennsylvania House of Representatives to benefit surrounding communities. This series includes information related to his involvement with various community and educational organizations, including Temple University, the State University of New York at Albany, the Heinz History Center, and various local, statewide, and national art foundations, among many others. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - 10000 Friends of Pennsylvania, 1996-1999 (Box 103, Folder 39)
    - 10000 Friends of Pennsylvania, 1998-1999 (Box 103, Folder 40)
    - Abidjan World Conference on World Peace, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 41)
    - Acknowledgements, An Effective Delivery System for the Aged, 1972 (Box 103, Folder 42)
    - Acknowledgements, Deny Me Not, undated (Box 103, Folder 43)
    - Acknowledgements, Poverty's Children, undated (Box 103, Folder 44)
    - Acknowledgements, Vocational Plan of Career Development for Female Residents of Correctional Facilities, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 45)
    - Addison Terrace Learning Center, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - African American Community Development, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Albany High School, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Alleghians LTD, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Allegheny Conference on Community Development, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny River Edge Park, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - American Youth Wind Orchestra, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Americans for Democratic Action, 1971, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - AMA Flying, 1997 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - American Waterways Wind Orchestra, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Arts Lottery, undated (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Bidwell, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Bishop McDevitt High School, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Black Caucus' Higher Education Leadership Summit, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1993 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Business and Job Development Corporation, Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - California State College of Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Carlow Cottage, 1994 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Carnegie Mellon, undated (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Center for Studying Social Welfare and Community Development, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Center on Race and Social Problems, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Century Technologies, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Cheyney University, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Child Development Program, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 26)
    - Citizens for Arts in Pennsylvania, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 27)
    - Civic Glossary, 1998 (Box 104, Folder 28)
    - Clarion University, 2005 (Box 104, Folder 29)
    - Community Action, Pittsburgh, 1968-1969 (Box 104, Folder 30)
    - Community College African American Caucus, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 31)
    - Community College of Allegheny County, 1995-1999 (Box 104, Folder 32)
    - Community College of Allegheny County, Legends in Leadership, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 33)
    - Connecticut Citizen Action Group, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 34)
    - Concord Resources Group, 1991-1992 (Box 104, Folder 35)
    - Council of the Americas, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - Crime Prevention, undated (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Daisy Lampkin Week, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 38)
    - David L. Lawrence Convention Center, 1998-1999 (Box 104, Folder 39)
    - David L. Lawrence Convention Center, Art Committee, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 40)
    - Declaration of Independence, Draft Resolution, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 41)
    - Division of Film Promotion, 1980 (Box 104, Folder 42)
    - Dominion Strong Men and Women, Excellence in Leadership, 2003 (Box 104, Folder 43)
    - Edinboro College, undated (Box 104, Folder 44)
    - Editing, undated (Box 104, Folder 45)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 46)
    - Fair Budget Coalition, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 47)
    - First Continental Congress Reconvened, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 48)
    - Forbes Field II Task Force, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 49)
    - Forbes Field II Task Force Committee Information, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 50)
    - Forbes Field II Task Force Committee Information, 1995 (Box 104, Folder 51)
    - Freedom Corner, 1999 (Box 104, Folder 52)
    - Gettysburg, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 53)
    - Governor's Conference on Library and Information Services, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 54)